<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Publish>
  <ModId Value="75804" />
  <DisplayName Value="Skyve [BETA]" />
  <ShortDescription Value="The all-in-one mod manager for Cities: Skylines II and PDX Mods" />
  <LongDescription>
Skyve is your all-in-one mod manager for Cities: Skylines II and PDX Mods.
It's a standalone application that you can use without opening the game, and it allows you to manage playsets, download or update your mods, browse PDX Mods, and much more.


# Installation
After adding Skyve to your playset, you will see a new button in the main menu called "Install Skyve".
This will start the one-click installation process and open the Skyve app at the end.

Once you've installed Skyve, you'll be able to find it in your apps list on Windows.

\* *Note that this is a standard application setup, which will prompt you for user account control permission. And it requires you to uninstall it from your apps list to completely remove it from your computer.*


# Features
## PDX Mods Integration
Skyve comes with the same PDX Mods capabilities as the game. Which means you'll be able to browse PDX Mods directly from Skyve, alongside:
* Subscribe and unsubscribe from mods.
* Download new mods, or update mods you're subscribed to.
* Manage playsets and enable/disable mods within them.

Skyve also comes with extensive bulk actions:
* Subscribe/unsubscribe/enable/disable multiple mods at a time.
* Add or remove mods from **all** your playsets at the same time.
* Merge or Exclude another playset's mods from your current playset.


## Compatibility Management
Skyve comes with an online compatibility catalogue.
This allows you to get real-time compatibility information about the mods that **you** are using.

Some, but not all, capabilities include:
* Warning you that a mod is not compatible with the latest patch of the game.
* Letting you know if a mod is broken or deprecated.
* Warning you if two or more mods that you are using are incompatible with each other, or if they have the same functionalities.
* Cautioning you about mods that break your save if you stop using them.
* Telling you that a mod you're using is succeeded by another newer mod.
* Letting you know if you're missing any requirements for your active mods.

Skyve will show you these warning while you're browsing mods, so you can know if a mod will cause you any issues before even subscribing to it.

You'll also have a dedicated compatibility report page that lists all the issues with your mods, and provides you with **one-click** button to fix them all at once.


### Management from outside of the game
Skyve is made to be used before you even open the game, and will update your mods without needing to open the game.

That way you **do not need** to wait for the updates to finish downloading in-game, then restart the game to start playing.

You can also freely browse for new mods and do some changes to your active playset without requiring a bunch of restarts.


## Stay up to date
When you install Skyve, you'll also get a small service that runs in the background and keeps your mods up-to-date.

If you miss Steam's auto-update feature where you didn't have to worry about having hundreds of updates to do after a long week... Then this is the answer.


## Help and Troubleshooting Issues
You'll find a dedicated Help and Logs tab in Skyve.
This tab allows you to quickly skim through any error that happened in your last gaming session.

And if you're not so sure about what the errors mean, you can use the Log Report feature to easily gather all needed files in one zip file which you can easily send to someone else so they can better assist you.

You'll soon also be able to use an automated troubleshoot process in Skyve to help guide you through the process of finding what mod(s) are causing issues.


# User Experience
Skyve is made with the attention to detail in mind. It aims to be easy to use, while also being easy on the eyes.

You can also customize the theme, colors, and UI scale of the app in the Theme Changer page (found in the Options or when right-clicking on the top bar)
</LongDescription>
  <Thumbnail Value="Properties/Release/Thumbnail.png" />
  <Screenshot Value="Properties/Release/Screenshot_01.png" />
  <Screenshot Value="Properties/Release/Screenshot_02.png" />
  <Screenshot Value="Properties/Release/Screenshot_03.png" />
  <Screenshot Value="Properties/Release/Screenshot_06.png" />
  <Screenshot Value="Properties/Release/Screenshot_07.png" />
  <Screenshot Value="Properties/Release/Screenshot_09.png" />
  <Screenshot Value="Properties/Release/Screenshot_10.png" />
  <Screenshot Value="Properties/Release/Screenshot_11.png" />
  <Screenshot Value="Properties/Release/Screenshot_12.png" />
  <Screenshot Value="Properties/Release/Screenshot_14.png" />
  <Tag Value="Code Mod" />
  <ForumLink Value="https://forum.paradoxplaza.com/forum/threads/skyve.1644654" />
  <ModVersion Value="0.12.6" />
  <GameVersion Value="1.*" />
  <ChangeLog>
# v0.12.6
## Hotfix
* Fixed backups getting created without a valid backup folder.
</ChangeLog>
  <ExternalLink Type="discord" Url="https://discord.gg/E4k8ZEtRxd" />
  <ExternalLink Type="github" Url="https://github.com/JadHajjar/Skyve" />
  <ExternalLink Type="crowdin" Url="https://crowdin.com/project/load-order-mod-2" />
  <ExternalLink Type="patreon" Url="https://www.patreon.com/tdwsvillage" />
</Publish>